Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Zines and APAs
  - Xenofilkia, Xenofilkia is a bimonthly fan zine run by Lee Gold. It is in print. Information about subscribing or purchasing issues can be found at https://www.conchord.org/xeno/.
    - Xenofilkia #133, 1 Oct 2010; 1 copy; Orange cover with cat and skeleton doing an el kabong with a guitar around a cauldron; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #133, 1 Oct 2010; 1 copy; Orange cover with cat and skeleton doing an el kabong with a guitar around a cauldron; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #134, 1 Dec 2010; 1 copy; Blue cover with Antarctic Summer Solistic Caroling with penguin; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #134, 1 Dec 2010; 1 copy; Blue cover with Antarctic Summer Solistic Caroling with penguin; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #135, 1 Feb 2011; 1 copy; Pink cover with valentine snowman with guitar; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #135, 1 Feb 2011; 1 copy; Pink cover with valentine snowman with guitar; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #136, 1 Apr 2011; 1 copy; Green cover with guitarist and dog hiking the stairway to heaven; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #136, 1 Apr 2011; 1 copy; Green cover with guitarist and dog hiking the stairway to heaven; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #137, 1 Jun 2011; 1 copy; Orange cover with cute animals, balloons and moon; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #137, 1 Jun 2011; 1 copy; Orange cover with cute animals, balloons and moon; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #138, 1 Aug 2011; 1 copy; Pirate flag pole with guitars a la maypole and a dog and cat; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #138, 1 Aug 2011; 1 copy; Pirate flag pole with guitars a la maypole and a dog and cat; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #139, 1 Oct 2011; 1 copy; Blue cover with cats in a basket and three mice (two are computer mice); genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #139, 1 Oct 2011; 1 copy; Blue cover with cats in a basket and three mice (two are computer mice); genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #140, 1 Dec 2011; 1 copy; White cover with musical notes snowing out of clouds onto trees; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #140, 1 Dec 2011; 1 copy; White cover with musical notes snowing out of clouds onto trees; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #141, 1 Feb 2012; 1 copy; Orange cover with Santa with guitar and reindeer; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #141, 1 Feb 2012; 1 copy; Orange cover with Santa with guitar and reindeer; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #142, 1 Apr 2012; 1 copy; Blue cover with guitarist on cloud with dog and sun and birds; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #143, 1 Jun 2012; 1 copy; Yellow cover with guitarist, moon and balloons; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #143, 1 June 2012; Gold, Lee; 1 copy; Yellow cover with balloon, moon and man with guitar; genreform: Zine; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - Xenofilkia #144, 1 August 2012; Gold, Lee; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover with musical notes and Ceasar Augustus; genreform: Zine; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - Xenofilkia #144, 1 Aug 2012; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover with musical notes and Ceasar Augustus; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #145, 1 Oct 2012; 1 copy; Pink cover with people singing to the Mars Rover; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #146, 1 Dec 2012; 1 copy; Yellow cover with giant turkey hovering over two vegetable farmers with guitars as only defense.; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #146, 1 Dec 2012; 1 copy; Yellow cover with giant turkey hovering over two vegetable farmers with guitars as only defense.; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #147, 1 Feb 2013; 1 copy; Blue cover with reindeer and snowman and guitarist in snow; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    - Xenofilkia #147, 1 Feb 2013; 1 copy; Blue cover with reindeer and snowman and guitarist in snow; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #148, 1 Apr 2013; 1 copy; Pink cover with dog, cat, musical instruments butterfly and bird.; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #149, 1 May 2013; 1 copy; Green cover with tiny people dancing with music, with birds and dog; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #150, 1 Aug 2013; 1 copy; Orange cover with Guitarist and cat at window and carolers.; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #151, 1 Oct 2013; 1 copy; Blue cover with figures singing, including ghosts and skeleton; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #152, 1 Dec 2013; 1 copy; Pink cover with people fighting over guitar; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #153, 1 Feb 2014; 1 copy; White cover with vase and faces illusion and musical notes.; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #154, 1 Apr 2014; 1 copy; Pink cover with mime and geometric shapes.; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #155, 1 Jun 2014; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover, musical sun; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #156, 1 Aug 2014; 1 copy; Yellow cover with collie and cat, with musical psychadelic roads; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
    - Xenofilkia #157, 1 Oct 2014; 1 copy; Blue cover with scale weighing earth and music; genreform: Zine (Box 15)
    - Xenofilkia #158, 1 Dec 2014; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #159, 1 Feb 2015; 1 copy; Yellow cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #161, 1 Jun 2015; 1 copy; Blue cover; genreform: Zine (Box 8)
    - Xenofilkia #162, 1 Aug 2015; 1 copy; Salmon cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #163, 1 Oct 2015; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #164, 1 Dec 2015; 1 copy; Green cover; genreform: Zine (Box 8)
    - Xenofilkia #165, 1 Feb 2016; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover; genreform: Zine (Box 9)
    - Xenofilkia, April #166 Filk's Daze, 1 copy; A filk APA produced by Lee Gold; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - Xenofilkia #167, 1 Jun 2016; 1 copy; Yellow cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #168, 1 Aug 2016; 1 copy; Green cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #169, 1 Oct 2016; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #170, 1 Dec 2016; 1 copy; Green cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #171, 1 Feb 2017; 1 copy; White cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #172, 1 Apr 2017; 1 copy; Pink cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #173, 1 Jun 2017; 1 copy; Light blue cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #174, 1 Aug 2017; 1 copy; Yellow cover; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
    - Xenofilkia #175, 1 Oct 2017; 1 copy; Goldenrod cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #176, 1 Dec 2017; 1 copy; Yellow cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #177, 1 Feb 2018; 1 copy; Blue cover; genreform: Zine (Box 9)
    - Xenofilkia #178, 1 Apr 2018; 1 copy; Pink cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #179, 1 Jun 2018; 1 copy; Yellow cover; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #180 (30th anniversary issue), 7 Sep 2018; 1 copy; Was sealed. Probably arrived after Harold was too sick to open it.; genreform: Zine (Box 7)
    - Xenofilkia #181, 1 Oct 2018; 1 copy; Pink cover; genreform: Zine (Box 11)
  - APA-Filk
    - Anakreon #14, 1 May 1982; 1 copy; Four sheets double sided; genreform: APA (Box 14)
    - Anakreon #23, 1 August 1984; 1 copy; Single pink page, single sided; genreform: APA (Box 14)
    - APA-Filk #22: Gone A-Maying, May 1984; 2 copies; Several stapled pages, lots of different segments from different dates; genreform: APA (Box 14, Box 15)
    - APA-Filk #31: Special Worldcon Issue, August 1986; 1 copy; White cover with cartoon of Union Soldiers; genreform: APA (Box 11)
      APA; Convention -- Worldcon
    - APA-Filk #34, May 1987; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA with internal blue pages; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #37, February 1988; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covred APA with a comic of the world as a vinyl record; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #38, May 1988; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #39, August 1988; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White colored APA with Far Side Cartoons, and a joke about Worldcon in New Orleans; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #40, November 1988; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA with interior pages in blue; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #41, February 1989; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covered APA with a cartoon of the number ten with filksongs falling out of it in a stream. There's also a reprint of the first lines of Happy birthday with a cease and desist.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #42, May 1989; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Light green covered APA with a cartoon of Zaphod Beeblebrox as a two headed George Washington; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #43 - No date listed, Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covered APA with spirograph style drawings; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #44, November 1989; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covered APA with a comic about the San Francisco earthquake; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #45, February 1990; Boardman, John; 2 copy; Comic covered APA; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #46, May 1990; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Pink covered issue with Anakreon on the front page (unusual); genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #47, July 1990; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Pink covered double APA - includes APA-Q # 319; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #48, November 1990; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered issue with Christmas themes; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #49, February 1991; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covered issue with Groucho Marx and Harpo Marx cartoon about war.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #50, May 1991; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #51, August 1, 1991, August 1991; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA, the numbering seems to duplicate an issue from later in the year that also claims to be #51; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #51, November 1991; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covered APA with Family Circus cartoon; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #53, 13th Anniversary, February 1992; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA, with blue pages in back.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #54, May 1992; Boardman, John; Rogow, Roberta; Blackman, Mark L.; Levine, Rennie; Browne, Mike; Housman, Mordecai; 1 copy; Comic covered APA with a ballot on the back APA-Filk multi-contributor filk fanzine from 1992. Contributors include John Boardman, Roberta Rogow, Mark L. Blackman, Rennie Levine, Mike Browne, Mordecai Housman. Features a double-sided ad for Concertino I "the Northeast Filk Convention", later NEFilk and the Northeast Floating Filk Convention.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #55, 1 August 1992; Boardman, John; 2 copy; White covered APA with angels playing instruments.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #57, 1 February 1993; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA with some pink pages; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #58, 1 May 1993; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA with some pages printed on light blue or bright blue paper.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #59, 1 August 1993; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #60, May 1993, Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered APA with some pages printed on pink paper and a half width insert ad for Science Fiction Mysteries and More (a defunct bookstore that was popular in NYC fandom).; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #61, February 1994; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Pink covered APA with a cartoon of Barney the Dinosaur holding money and singing - 15th Anniversary issue.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #62, May 1994; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Blue covered APA with a picutre of the Beatles.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #63, August 1994; Boardman, John; 2 copies; Yellow covered APA with a pigeon in a suit, smoking an olive branch on a mountain.; genreform: APA (Box 2, Box 11)
    - APA-Filk #64, November 1994; 1 copy; Yellow cover with number; genreform: APA (Box 11)
    - APA-Filk #65, February 1995; Boardman, John; 1 copy; White covered issue with Betty Boop cartoon; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #66, 1 May 1995; Boardman, John; 1 copy; Comic covered issue with Anakreon label; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #66 - In Memoriam, May 1995; Boardman, John; 2 copies; White covered issue with a cartoon of a mushroom cloud and a kazoo; genreform: APA (Box 2, Box 11)
    - APA-Filk #67: Special Scottish Worldcon Disty, 1 copy; White cover with Scottsman; genreform: APA (Box 11)
    - APA-Filk #68, November 1995, Boardman, John; 1 copy; White issues with a smashed guitar, this appears to have been the last issue.; genreform: APA (Box 2)
    - APA-Filk #68: The Day the Music Died, November 1995; 2 copy; White cover with broken guitar; genreform: APA (Box 11)
  - Mind Music: A Tomorrow People Fanzine, 2003; 1 copy; Purple cover with a man's head in a human hand; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
    Zine; Fandom -- Tomorrow People
  - A Few Subversive Ciphers by rap legend Jesse Dangerously and Friends, Dangerously, Jessie (Box 7)
  - Brotherly Love: Being a Tale of the Hooded Man, 1 copy; Includes prose and songs, pink with celtic knotwork letters, staple bound; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
  - Immaculate Confusion Songbook, 1 copy; Orange cover with a person harping. Printed on yellow paper, held together with a paperclip. Art by Robin Wood! What is filk, listing of filk resources.; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
  - FAN-tastic Filk Song and other Fannish Delights, 1982; Eric Gerds; 1 copy; White with line art illustration with people in various poses; genreform: Zine (Box 8)
  - The Liberated Tardis Trek, 1989; 1 copy; White cover, staple bound, one-shot fanzine; genreform: Zine (Box 14)
  - Fresh Beaver Tales - Fan fiction zine, 1992; Rogow, Roberta; Publisher Peg Kennedy; Bill Hupe, Footrot Flats; Footrot Flats; 1 copy; Story by Roberta Rogow. Copyright 1992, Publisher Peg Kennedy and Bill Hupe, Footrot Flats; genreform: Zine (Box 8)
  - Loose Notes: A Zine for Filky-Minded Fans, circa 1980s; 1 copy; White cover with filkers being very far from the hotel, staple bound; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
  - The Compleat Dirty Nelly, 1991; Rogow, Roberta; T'kuhtian Press; 1 copy; Star Trek Fan fiction collection; genreform: Zine (Box 8)
  - Friends & Strangers, Near & Far: A Filk/Poetry/Art Fanzine, 1980; 1 copy; Yellow cover with title, square bound with plastic; genreform: Zine (Box 16)
  - Let's Filk About #3, 1994; 1 copy; Light grey cover with fire lizards; genreform: Zine; genreform: Songbook (Box 2)
  - Rec-Room Rhymes Omnibus, Rogow, Roberta; 1 copy; Notes: Sepia cover with fancy printing Origin: Rogow, Roberta; genreform: Songbook (Box 2)
  - Rec Room Rhymes, Omnibus, 1990; Rogow, Roberta; 1 copy; Notes: Loose sheets, unbound Origin: Originated 1982, 3rd printing 1990; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 2)
  - Rec Room Rhymes, Second Omnibus, 1990; Rogow, Roberta; Pegasus Publications; 1 copy; Notes: Loose sheets, unbound Origin: Originated 1986, 3rd printing, 1990 from Pegasus Publications; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 2)
  - Rec Room Rhymes #18, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Cover says "Rack Room" Origin: Rogow, Roberta; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 15)
  - Rec Room Rhymes #18, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Cover says "Rack Room" Origin: Rogow, Roberta; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 16)
  - Musical Chas - A filksong fanzine vol 1 no 1, CHASFANS; 1 copy; Notes: This appears to have originated with The Capitol Hill Area Science Fiction and Narcissism Society Origin: CHASFANS; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 2)
  - Musical Chas - A filksong fanzine Vol 2. Number 2, CHASFANS; 1 copy; Notes: This appears to have originated with The Capitol Hill Area Science Fiction and Narcissism Society Origin: CHASFANS; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 2)
  - Musical Chas - Last issue, CHASFANS; 1 copy; Notes: This appears to have originated with The Capitol Hill Area Science Fiction and Narcissism Society Origin: CHASFANS; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 2)
  - FAN-tastic Filk Songs and other Fannish Delights, July-September Vol 1. No. 1, Gerds, Eric; 1 copy; Notes: Glossy cover with spaceship and a fan swimming in space Origin: Gerds, Eric; genreform: Fanzine / Songbook (Box 2)
- Conventions
  - Archon
    - Archon 35, 2011
      - Archon 35 Filk Book Songbook, 2011; 2 copy; genreform: Songbook (Box 13, Box 14)
        Notes: Blue cover with chthulu playing guitar, John Sies, cover art. Cat Morrese and Bari Greenberg did the layout Convention: Archon 35
        General
        Convention -- Archon 35; Songbook
    - Archon 36, 2012
      - Archon 36 Filk Book Songbook, 2012; 2 copy; Notes: Layout by Sandra and Bari Greenberg, cover has the Orion Nebua. Spiral bound, glossy book Convention: Archon 36:; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
        Convention -- Archon 36; Songbook
    - Archon 38, 2014
      - Archon 38 Songbook Songbook, 2013; Archon 39, 2014; 4 copy; Notes: Produced for Archon 38 Convention: Archon 38, 2014; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Might actually be Archon 39
        Convention -- Archon 38 (2013); Songbook
    - Archon 39, 02 Oct 2015 to 04 Oct 2015
      - Archon 39 Songbook Songbook, 2015; Archon 39; 2 copy; Notes: Produced for Archon 38 Origin: Archon 39, 2015 Convention: Archon 39; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- Archon 39; Songbook
      - Archon 39 Filk Book Songbook, 2015; 1 copy; Notes: White cover with arches Origin: Mountain Cat Media Convention: Archon 39; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
    - Archon 40, 29 Sep 2017 to 01 Oct 2017
      - Archon 40 Songbook Songbook, 2016; Archon 40, 2016; 2 copy; Notes: Produced for Archon 40, Spiral bound Convention: Archon 40, 2016; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- Archon 40 (2016); Songbook
    - Archon 41, 2014
      - Archon 41 Filk Book Songbook, 2017; 2 copy; Notes: Blue cover with with abstract shapes and rocket, Katrina Joyner, cover art. Cat Greenberg did the layout, Loose song Falcon Nine is tucked into the book Origin: Mountain Cat Media Convention: Archon 41; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
        Convention -- Archon 41; Songbook
  - Arisia
    - Arisia 2008, 18 Jan 2008 to 21 Jan 2008
      - Arisia 2008 Sunday Night Open Filk, Arisia 2008; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Contains truncated files due (we think) to the file writing system Harold was using having a 2 GB limit. The files are still readable to that point, thank Ghu. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Arisia 2008; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
        Convention -- Arisia 2008; CD -- Burnt
      - Arisia 2008 Saturday Night Open FIlk, Arisia 2008; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Contains truncated files due (we think) to the file writing system Harold was using having a 2 GB limit. The files are still readable to that point, thank Ghu. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Arisia 2008; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
  - Balticon
    - Balticon 44, 28 May 2010 to 31 May 2010
      Baltimore, MD
    - Balticon 47, 24 May 2013 to 27 May 2013
      - Sundown - Whispers of Ragnarok: Norse Myth Song Cycle, 2014; Sassafras; Palmer, Ada; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Ada Palmer Convention: Balticon 47: 2013; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
        Convention -- Balticon 47: 2013; CD -- Commercial
      - Sundown: Whispers of Ragnarok, 2013; Sassafras; Palmer, Ada; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Ada Palmer Convention: Balticon 47: 2013; genreform: Commercial DVD (Box 5)
        Convention -- Balticon 47: 2013; Commercial DVD
    - Balticon Filkbook, 1992; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with squirrel and several marks on tree Origin: Convention: Balticon 26; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
      Convention -- Balticon 26; Songbook
    - Balticon 2004 - 1 Discs 1-3, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: Balticon 38: 2004; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      Convention -- Balticon 38: 2004; MiniDisc
    - Balticon BL - Disc 2, 2004; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: Balticon 38: 2004; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - BLTCN - 3 Balticon 2004 Disc 3, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #6 Origin: Convention: Balticon 38: 2004; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Balticon 51 - Baltimore Science Fiction Society, 2017; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow flier, double sided Origin: May 26-29, 2017; genreform: Flier (Box 9)
      Flier; ephemera
  - BayFilk
    - Bayfilk 1, 05 Mar 1982 to 07 Mar 1982
      - Bayfilk Not So Instant Songbook, 1982; Bayfilk 1, 1982; Off Centaur Publications; 3 copy; Notes: Green cover with dumptruck Origin: Off Centaur Publications, 1982 Convention: Bayfilk 1; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
        Convention -- Bayfilk 1 (1982); Songbook
      - BayFilk I Program and Songbook, 1982; 1 copy; Notes: Lime green cover with dumptruck dumping musical notes, staple bound Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 14)
        Convention -- Bayfilk 1 (1982); Songbook; Program Book
      - BayFilk I Program and Songbook, 1982; 1 copy; Notes: Lime green cover with dumptruck dumping musical notes, staple bound Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 16)
      - Bayfilk Not So Instant Songbook, 1982; Bayfilk 1, 1982; Off Centaur Publications; 1 copy; Notes: Green cover with dumptruck Origin: Off Centaur Publications, 1982 Convention: Bayfilk 1: 1982; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
    - Bayfilk II, 02 Mar 1984 to 04 Mar 1984
      - BayFilk II Program and Songbook, 1984; 1 copy; Notes: Lime green cover with excavator picking up musical notes Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II: 1984; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 16)
        Convention -- Bayfilk II (1984); Songbook; Program Book
    - Bayfilk 5, 03 Mar 1989 to 05 Mar 1989
      - Bayfilk 5, 1989, March 3-5, 1 copy; Notes: Neon green cover with classical musician Schedule of events Origin: Bayfilk 5 Convention: Bayfilk 5; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Bayfilk 5; Program booklet
    - BayFilk Progress Report 2, 1994; 1 copy; Notes: Light grey-green pamphlet style, staple bound Origin: Off Centaur Publications Convention: Bayfilk II: 1984; genreform: Progress report (Box 14)
      Convention -- Bayfilk II (1984); Progress report
    - Concert On Stage, Bayfilk III; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: - Convention: Bayfilk III; genreform: Convention CD (Box 1)
      Convention -- BayFilk III; CD -- Convention
    - BayFilk III Songbook: It Was Late ..., 1 copy; Notes: Light green cover with bulldozer riding over musical notes, spiral bound Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
      Convention -- BayFilk III; Songbook
    - BayFilk Albums, BayFilk; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Commercial tapes Convention: BayFilk; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- BayFilk; CD -- Burnt
  - Boskone
    - Boskone 14, 18 Feb 1977 to 20 Feb 1977
      - The Boskone 14 Filkson Supplement to the NESFA Hymnal, 1977; Boskone 14, 1977; NESFA, Inc.; 1 copy; Notes: Orangy cover with a multi-armed alien at the MIT post office. Origin: NESFA, Inc. Convention: Boskone 14; genreform: Songbook (Box 2)
        Convention -- Boskone 14; Songbook
    - Boskone 45, 15 Feb 2008 to 17 Feb 2008
      - Boskone 45 Program book, 2008; Boskone 45, February 15-17, 2008; 1 copy; Notes: White booklet Convention: Boskone 45; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- Boskone 45; Program booklet
    - Boskone 49, 2012
      - Gary McGath schedule for Boskone 49, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: White single sided page Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; genreform: Convention Documents (Box 14)
        Convention -- Boskone 49 (2012); Convention Documents